import '/models/question.dart';

const List<Question> mathQuestions = [
  Question(
    question: '1. What is 5 + 7?',
    correctAnswerIndex: 2,
    options: ['10', '11', '12', '13'],
  ),
  Question(
    question: '2. What is 9 - 4?',
    correctAnswerIndex: 0,
    options: ['5', '6', '7', '4'],
  ),
  Question(
    question: '3. What is 6 × 3?',
    correctAnswerIndex: 1,
    options: ['15', '18', '20', '16'],
  ),
  Question(
    question: '4. What is 15 ÷ 3?',
    correctAnswerIndex: 3,
    options: ['6', '7', '4', '5'],
  ),
  Question(
    question: '5. What is the square root of 64?',
    correctAnswerIndex: 2,
    options: ['6', '7', '8', '9'],
  ),
  Question(
    question: '6. What is 2³ (2 to the power of 3)?',
    correctAnswerIndex: 0,
    options: ['8', '6', '9', '4'],
  ),
  Question(
    question: '7. What is the value of π (pi) approximately?',
    correctAnswerIndex: 1,
    options: ['3.12', '3.14', '3.15', '3.16'],
  ),
  Question(
    question: '8. What is 100% of 50?',
    correctAnswerIndex: 3,
    options: ['25', '75', '45', '50'],
  ),
  Question(
    question: '9. What is 7 × 7?',
    correctAnswerIndex: 2,
    options: ['42', '48', '49', '56'],
  ),
  Question(
    question: '10. What is 20% of 200?',
    correctAnswerIndex: 0,
    options: ['40', '50', '60', '30'],
  ),
];
